Guide to the Progressive Student Union records, RG0134
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Campaigns, 1966-2008; 1989-1996; Series 2; 5 Linear Feet
  - Racism, 1966-1999; 1989-1996; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 8
    - Racism, 1990-1994; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 8 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Native Americans and anti-Columbus, 1986-1994; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 8 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Black history month, 1989-1992; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 8 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Anti-semitism, 1991-1995; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 8 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Immigration, 1992-1996; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 8 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - White supremacy, 1995-1999; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 8 (Box R1, Folder 17, Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Minority enrollment statistics and stuff, 1989-1992; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 8 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Black power, 1966-1995; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 8 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Organizations, 1970-2003; 1990-1996; Series 3; 4.5 Linear Feet
      Organizations
      The materials of this series include brochures, educational material, event flyers, information flyers, organizational records, correspondence, solicitation letters, articles, newsletters, campaign material, contact information, material from conferences, and fact sheets. The material dates from 1970 to 2003, but it is predominately from 1990 to 1996. This series contains items created by various international, national, regional, city, and student organizations whose beliefs and/or agendas were favored by the GW Progressive Student Union. Students from the Progressive Student Union worked with some of these organizations; Rusty Stahl was a leader in multiple student organizations for example. In other cases, the Progressive Student Union simply collected information from other organizations. Information about the Progressive Student Network is contained within this series. Arrangement is alphabetical.
      Organizations folders are arranged alphabetically by organization title.
      - Acorn and grassroots community organizing, 1989-1995; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - ACLU, undated; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - ACT-UP / DC and national, 1990-1991; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - ADA and YDA, 1995-1997; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - ADA and YDA II, 1993-1996; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - AFL-CIO, 1982-2001; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - AIPAC, 1994; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - AlterNet, undated; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Americorps, circa 1996; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Amnesty International, 1996-1999; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Auto-free DC, spring 1994; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Beehive Collective, 1993-1994; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Calvary Womens Shelter, undated; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Center for Campus Organizing, 1996-2000; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - Center for Campus Organizing / University Conversion Project, 1992-1995; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - Committee in Solidarity with the People of El Salvador (CISPES), 1989-1991; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - College Democrats I, 1995-1996; RG0134 Series 3 (Box R1, Folder 20, Box 15, Folder 17)
      - College Democrats II, 1994-1995; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - DC Activist Circle, 1996; RG0134 Series 3 (Box R1, Folder 21, Box 15, Folder 19)
      - DC Students Acting for Justice, 1995; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - DC Men Against Rape, 1992-1994; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Democratic Party, circa 1995; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - East Timor Action Network, 1991-1993; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Empty the Shelters, 1991-1992; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Fairness and Accuracy in Reporting (FAIR), circa 1990; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - FMLA / Voices for Choices, undated; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Friends of the Earth, 1990-1996; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Global Exchange - Fair Trade, 1999-2000; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Greenpeace, 1985-1990; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Greenpeace, 1989-1995; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Greens, 1990-1992; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Georgetown PSU, 1991-1992; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - GWAC, 2001; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - GW Voices, 1985-1988; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Habitat for Humanity, circa 1995; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - Homes Not Jails / Health DC, circa 2001; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - International Campaign to Ban Landmines, undated; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - Jews United for Justice, 2001; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - Jobs with Justice, 1988-2000; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 20)
      - Justice Policy Institute, 1996-1997; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 21)
      - Kennedy Institute, 1994; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 22)
      - Kensington Welfare Rights Union, 1998-2000; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 23)
      - Labor Party, 1999-2000; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 24)
      - Maoist International Movement, 1992-1996; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 25)
      - Miriams Kitchen, 1983-1993; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - National Audubon Society, 1988-1992; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - National Lawyers Guild, 1999-2000; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - National Park Conservation Association, 1994; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - National Student News Service, 1990; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - National Wildlife Federation, 1991-1994; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - National Wildlife Federation II, 1989-1994; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Neighborhood Assistance Corporation of America, circa 1990s; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Oxfam, circa 1991; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - PCRM / PETA, undated; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Peace Action, 1995-2000; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Peace Brigades International, 1993; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - PIRG, 1977-1990; RG0134 Series 3 (Box R1, Folder 22, Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Positive Force DC, undated; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - PSN organization, 1980-1990; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - PSN Correspondence, 1990-1991; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - PSN correspondence, 1991-1992 school year; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - PSN fall 1992 conference, RG0134 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - PSN correspondence, 1992-1993 school year; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - PSN correspondence, 1993-1994 school year; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - PSN promo lit and info originals, circa 1989 - circa 1990; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - PSRU - People for a Socially Responsible University, 1988-1991; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Queer Nation, 1991-1992; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Radical Student Union, 1970; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Rainbow / ROYC, 1994-1995; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Refuse and Resist, 1989-1991; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - Republican Party, 1995; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - Sanibel Captiva Conservation Foundation, 1991-1994; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - SCAR, DC - Student Coalition Against Aparthied and Racism, 1989-1992; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 16)
      - SEA - Students for Enviromental Action, 1990-1992; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Share the Wealth Project, 1995; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 18)
      - Sierra Club, 1989-1992; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 19)
      - Socialist Workers / International Socialist Organization, 1999; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 20)
      - SPAN - Student Peace Action Network, 1997-1999; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 21)
      - SPAN - Student Peace Action Network, 1998-1999; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 22)
      - SSDP - Students for a Sensible Drug Policy, 1990-1999; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Student Action Alliance, 1996-1997; RG0134 Series 3 (Box R1, Folder 23, Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Student Action Union, 1990-1992; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Students Against War in Iraq, 2002-2003; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Student Environmental Action Coalition, 1989-1993; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - United Students Against Sweatshops, 1998-2001; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - United Students Against Sweatshops (USAS), 1999; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - United States Student Association, 1991-2000; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - VISTA, circa 1991; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Washington Peace Center, circa 1992; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - War Resisters League - WRL, 1990-1991; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - War Tax Resisters, 1998-1999; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - Whitman-Walker Clinic, circa 1995; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - The Wilderness Society, 1985-1992; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - Women Take Action, 1995-1996; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - Young Americans for Freedom, 1989-1993; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - Young Koreans United - YKU, 10/1991; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - Young Socialist Alliance and Mark Curtis, 1990-1996; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - Zero Population Growth, 1992-1997; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 19)
      - 180 Movement for Democracy and Education Clearinghouse, 1999; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 20)
      - 2030 Center, circa 1994; RG0134 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - War and Peace, 1982-2007; 1989-1996; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 9
    - NATO, circa 1999; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 9 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Gulf War, 1990-1991; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 9 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Draft registration, 1987-1991; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 9 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Covert operation, 1988-1992; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 9 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Demilitarisation / democracy, 1990-2000; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 9 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Nukes, 1982-1996; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 9 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Nuclear war, 1982-1992; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 9 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - War in general, 1992-2007; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 9 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Women's Issues, 1978-2008; 1989-1996; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 10
    - Mens pledge to end sexism, 1991-1994; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Womens global issues, 1991-1992; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Random womens press, 1990; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Violence against women, 1990-1995; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Ecofeminism, 1990-1991; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Wimmins sexuality, 1991; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Wimmins liberation, 1978-2008; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Wimmins History Month, 1990-1996; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Abortion background info, 1983-1993; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Pro-choice, 1989-1992; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Other Campaigns/Issues, 1970-2006; 1989-1996; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11
    - Anarchy, 1985-1991; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Ayn Rand, 1985; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - GW bricks file, 1990; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Childrens issues, undated; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - CIA off campus, 1986-1992; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Deutsch, Cheryl, spring 2006; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box R1, Folder 18, Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Drugs, 1997-1999; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Economic conversion, 1990-1995; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Ethics and meaning and other positive stuff, circa 1990s; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Flag burning, 1989; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Gun control, 1990-1995; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Homeless DC, 1987-2001; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box R1, Folder 19, Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Community Service, 1995-1996; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Media bias, 1990-1993; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Nader, Ralph, 2000; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Olin Corp., 1989-1991; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Pacifica/indepentent radio, 1999-2000; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Performing arts, undated; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Police Brutality, 1992-1995; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Political correct, circa 1991; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Political campaigns, 1994-1997; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Population org, 1990-1992; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Pornography, undated; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Prison issues, circa 1993 - circa 1994; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Religious stuff, 1983-1999; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Senior citizens, circa 1995; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Sexual issues, circa 1993 - circa 1994; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Social security, summer 1999; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Socialism, communism, or other leftist movements, 1994-1997; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Washington DC issues, 1994-1997; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Weatherman, 1970; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Wide variety of social justice statistics, 1992; RG0134 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Periodicals, 1987-2002; 1990-1996; Series 4; 3 Linear Feet
  Periodicals
  The materials of this series include newspapers, newsletters, and magazines. The material dates from 1987 to 2002, but it is predominately from 1990 to 1996. The articles in these periodicals generally express progressive, liberal, or radical views. The periodicals were collected and kept by the Progressive Student Union. Periodicals are in alphabetical order by title. This series includes the GW Progressive Student Union publications Unfiltered and Buff and Blue.
  The bulk of the periodicals folders are arranged alphabetically by periodical title. Within each folder, issues are arranged chronologically. Some periodicals are arranged in group folders at the end of the series.
  - Alert! Back Issues, 05/1990 - 01/1992; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Amnesty Action, 05/1989-12/1990; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Buff-N-Blue, 12/1990- spring 1992; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Campus Report, 09/1990-05/2000; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Capital Area Peace Studies, 10/1989-04/1991; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - The Circle: News from an American Indian Perspective, 03/1991-09/1991; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Columbia College Alumni Newsletter, spring 1992; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - E: The Environmental Magazine / EA: Environmental Action, 07/1990-08/1992; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Education for the People, 11/1990 - winter 1993; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Forest Voice, 09/1989-1990; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Forward Motion, 12/1992-4/1993; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Green Calendar, 09/1990-04/1994; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Green Update, fall 1996 - winter 1997; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - The Guardian, 01/30/1991-04/15/1992; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - GW periodicals, 12/7/2001-02/27/2002; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - In These Times, 01/10/1990-02/20/1990; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - In These Times II, 02/21/1990-04/10/1990; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - In These Times III, 04/11/1990-01/19/1997; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Independence Magazine, 02/04/1998; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Infusion, 11/1997-10/1998; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - The Irish People, 05/29/1999-05/06/2000; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Korea Report, 05/1987-09/1991; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Love and Rage, 07/1992-02/1998; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - The Messenger, 09/1998-02/2000; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - MIM Notes, 03/1993-02/1996; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - The Minuteman, 05/16/1988-05/1991; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Mother Jones, 07/1994-02/2000; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - The Nation, 06/1991-04/1993; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - The Nation, 05/1993-08/1993; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - The Nation, 09/1993-11/1993; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - The Nation, 12/1996-02/1997; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - The Nation, 03/03/1997-03/31/1997; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - The Nation, 09/1999-12/1999; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - The Nation, 01/31/2000-03/13/2000; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - The Nation, 04/03/2000-5/15/2000; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Native City News, 08/15/1991-08/22/1991; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - New Liberation News Service, 01/04/1990-05/4/1992; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - The New Republic, 10/3/1994-10/10/1994; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Nonviolent Activist Magazine, 09/1990-08/1991; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Off Our Backs, 04/1992-01/1994; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - PCRM Update, 01/1987-10/1989; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Peoples Weekly World, 11/5/1994-10/14/2000; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - PSN News, 09/1991 - fall 1994; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Say, 09/1994-10/1995; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - SCAR News, 12/1987 - winter 1993; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Socialist Action, 06/1999-05/2000; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - The Thistle, 02/03/1993-10/20/1993; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Threshold, 05/1991-01/1993; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Toward Freedom, 03/1991-12/1991; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Unfiltered, 11/1995-04/1997; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - War Research Info Service, 08/1991-09/1992; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Washington Peace Letters I, 02/1990-11/1991; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Washington Peace Letter II, 02/1992-10/1994; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Washington Peace Letter III, 11/1994-08/2000; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Washington Peace Letter Action Guide, 12/1995-01/1998; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - The Washington Spectator, 05/15/1995-06/1/1995; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Workers Vanguard, 11/18/1988-11/5/1993; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Z Magazine, 09/1993-04/1995; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Progressive publications A-B, 11/1991 - spring 2000; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Progressive publications C-F, 05/1988 - winter 2001; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Progressive publications G-N, 02/1993-05-2000; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Progressive publications O-R, 10/1990-03/1998; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Progressive publications S-Y, 12/1990-04/2000; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Misc. alternative college presses, 01/1988-03/1997; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Historical paper - ones we just don't want to throw out, 12/1990-03/1995; RG0134 Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Memorabilia, circa 1990 - circa 2004; 1990-2004; Series 5; 1 Linear Feet
  Memorabilia
  The materials of this series include political and social campaign buttons and a plaque. Items date from the 1990s and early 2000s.
  All memorabilia is contained in one box.
  - Political and social campaign buttons and plaque, circa 1990 - circa 2004; RG0134 Series 5 (Box 26)